<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R on Dongsun Cao</title>
    <link>/categories/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R on Dongsun Cao</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A practial guide to create a web site in 4 steps using Blogdown</title>
      <link>/post/create-a-web-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/create-a-web-site/</guid>
      <description>Get StartedPutting up your personal web site in the internet is everyone’s dream. There are numerous web site building platforms out there, like wix, [WordPress]https://wordpress.com/. Of those sites, WordPress is the most popular. It provides you a suite of serve to create a beautiful web site, either blog or e-commence site. Using WordPress, you do not need to know Programming like HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
However, all those service comes with some of costs despite the cost may be minimal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shiny Application: Use of Cluster Anlysis to Detect Multiple Enrollments in Clinical Trials</title>
      <link>/post/shiny-application-use-of-cluster-anlysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/shiny-application-use-of-cluster-anlysis/</guid>
      <description>AbstractMultiple enrollment refers to a practice of a patient taking part in a clinical trial at more than two sites within same study or in multiple studies within same clinical program.
Patients seek multiple enrollments for a variety of reasons. Some seek more access to the study drugs while others are seeking additional compensations. Whatever reasons, multiple enrollments by a single patient at different sites in a study or across studies compromises the data integrity and jeopardizes the patient’s safety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R MarkdownThis is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars)## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>