<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R Markdown on Dongsun Cao</title>
    <link>/tags/r-markdown/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R Markdown on Dongsun Cao</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/r-markdown/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Use of Shiny and Leaflet to Monitor Observer Agreement in Psoriasis Assessments</title>
      <link>/post/monitor-observer-agreement-in-psoriasis-assessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/monitor-observer-agreement-in-psoriasis-assessment/</guid>
      <description>PsoriasisPsoriasis (PSO) is a chronic inflammatory disease characterized by a series of linked cellular changes in the skin: hyperplasia of epidermal keratinocytes, vascular hyperplasia and ectasia, and infiltration of T lymphocytes, neutrophils, and other types of leukocytes in affected skinIn the clinical studies, Psoriasis severity are usually assessed by multiple methods including psoriasis area and severity index (PASI), Body surface Area (BSA), and Investigator’s Global Assessment (IGA).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A concise guide to create a web site in 4 steps using Blogdown</title>
      <link>/post/create-a-web-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/create-a-web-site/</guid>
      <description>Get Started:Putting up your personal web site in the internet is everyone’s dream. There are numerous web site building platforms out there, like Wix or WordPress. Of those tools, WordPress is the most popular. It provides you a suite of service to create a beautiful web site, either blog or e-commence site. Using WordPress, you do not need to know how to code like HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R MarkdownThis is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars)## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>